<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phillip Marlowe Professional Engineer</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Phillip Marlowe Professional Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:50:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:50:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;gotta-start-somewhere&#34;&gt;Gotta Start Somewhere&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that my Masters project is coming to a close, I am starting to get moments of breathing room that have allowed me to produce this minimal website/blog to showcase my professional and academic projects as well as other professional knowledge about me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Phillip Marlowe is an electronics engineer with a strong foundation in digital design and physical implementation, recently graduating from UC Santa Cruz with a master’s degree in Computer Engineering. He has developed a semi-general physical design flow focused on the back end, originally intended for RTL generated by PRGA, but flexible enough to accommodate any RTL on any PDK supported by Cadence physical design tools. His flow enables pushing FPGA CLBs, tiles, and complete eFPGA architectures all the way from RTL to GDSII, bridging the gap between high-level design and manufacturable layouts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic/Professional Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semi General Physical Design Flow for eFPGA RTL&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During my masters, I&amp;rsquo;ve developed a semi-general, semi-automated physical design flow for ASIC/FPGA that has been used to produce multiple real designs, including an N8 K4 4×4 FPGA, an N2 K4 8×8 FPGA, and several smaller blocks such as individual FPGA tiles, CLBs, and buffer chains. All of these designs are implemented using open-source process design kits (PDKs). The primary target has been the ASAP7 PDK from ASU, while the FreePDK45 (Free45nm) from NC State has been used to produce a CLB in an alternative process node. This project focuses on building a reusable, configurable back-end flow that can take FPGA-style RTL through to layout on modern open PDKs, enabling rapid experimentation with different architectures and technology nodes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
